## **AARON CURTIS MAHABIR**

Software Engineer

#### **EDUCATION**

**BrainStation I Diploma, Web Development** 2022, TORONTO, ON

Conestoga College I Bachelors in Engineering 2019, CAMBRIDGE, ON

# Conestoga College | Diploma Mechanical Engineering Tech

2017, CAMBRIDGE, ON

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Line Cook | Tam: Vietnamese Street Food and Cafe

OCT 2021 - PRESENT, TORONTO, ON

- Boosted restaurant revenue by creating and maintaining good rapport with customers
- Managed and fulfilled all incoming orders to back of house while coordinating with front of house to provide an optimal customer experience
- Established a community through networking at festivals and events (Smorgasburg, Taste of Vietnam, etc.)

### Hydraulic Estimator | Berendsen Fluid Power

2020 - 2021, MARKHAM, ON

- Assessed and integrated necessary changes to hydraulic schematics for future iterations of projects.
- Communicated with vendors to ensure that project budgets and timelines were feasible

## Mechanical Designer | Starquip Industries

2019 - 2020, TORONTO, ON

- Conceptualized, designed, and constructed functional 3D models for indoor gantry crane components
- Collaborated with project managers to deliver renderings of designs to clients

#### **PROJECTS**

## Coder | PokemonUltimateTeam

2022 - BrainStation Capstone Project

 Using React.js, Node.js and Mysql. Created a site that allows users to make and analyze pokemon teams of their choice. aaroncurtis32@gmail.com 647-294-1421 https://www.linkedin.com/in/ aaronmahabir/ https://github.com/aaroncm5

#### **PROFILE**

I am working to build my career as a software engineer and deepen my experience in coding.

I am known as a diligent and independent worker, and willing to consult and seek advice when needed.

Adaptable to new situations, and able to pick up new tasks quickly. When working within a team I am forward thinking, can remain calm in stressful situations, and always helpful and supportive to co workers.

Accountability and opportunities to learn are key personal values

## **SKILLS**

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node, MySQL, Agile Development, Document Object Model (DOM) API's, Web API's, User Authentication, OAuth, Heroku, Jest, React, Node.Js, Ruby, Rails Google Analytics, GitHub, SolidWorks, AutoCAD